pollfish.com 2013-10-21

# Pollfish: Privacy policy

Privacy policy

This privacy policy applies to all services and products provided by Pollfish. The following paragraphs explain how Pollfish use and handle your personal data. 

Privacy policy is presented in a more friendly and appealing way in order to help you quickly find the answers you really want about the privacy practices used by Pollfish. 

**Privacy Policy Highlights – Things that matter to you**

For those creating surveys: 

  * Your survey data belong to you and will never be seen, accessed, sold or delivered to anyone. Your survey data though can be used by the platform for better targeting and assisting the skipping logic of future surveys. 
  * Your survey data are stored and kept securely at servers in the United States. 
  * Your survey data are processed and delivered to you at your wish. 

For those answering surveys: 

  * Survey responses are collected anonymously. 
  * Survey responses are not disclosed or sold to any third party. The survey creator controls your responses. 
  * You will be prompted to provide your email only in case that you will be awarded. This information is kept securely, not disclosed to anyone and used only for informing you on how you will get your award. 
  * Pollfish is the middleman responsible for delivering your responses to the survey creator. The survey creator is responsible for the content of the survey and the provided responses. 

For those integrating Pollfish into their apps 

  * Only public information about you app is collected when you integrate Pollfish in your app. 
  * Pollfish monitors and inform you about the survey responses gathered through your app. 
  * Statistics and behavior of users on each survey served through your app are collected and stored to Pollfish servers. 

**Privacy Policies**

**Survey Creators – Survey Respondents – App Developers**

Through a Pollfish survey lifecycle three are the key players that take part, Survey Creators, Survey Respondents and App Developers. Information used from each player is different and therefore is handled differently in the following privacy policies. 

**Survey Creators**

What information does Pollfish collect about you? 

Registration Information. In order to create a survey you have to register and create an account by providing your email and password. Survey data. Pollfish stores your survey content and delivers it to you upon request. 

How does Pollfish treat your information? 

Your survey data are kept securely and not disclosed to any third party for any reason. Your survey data maybe used by the platform for better targeting and skipping logic on future surveys. Your survey data are kept and delivered to you at any time and available format upon your request. Your registration information are kept securely and not disclosed to any third party for any reason. Your registration information data maybe used during assistance or customer support for providing better services to you. Your registration information maybe used for contacting you occasionally (for platform announcements, account activation etc.) Your registration information maybe used to respond to legal claims by your survey users to inspect the survey data and act or respond accordingly. 

When and with whom we will share your information? 

We do not disclose any of your information to any third party marketing or advertising agency. We may disclose your information only as permitted and required by the law in cases such as to protect Pollfish rights, such as court orders or any other legal process served on us. 

What actions can you make on your information? 

You can update your registration information at any time You can export and download your data at any time in the available provided formats To cancel or delete your account you should contact Pollfish team with your request at info@pollfish.com. 

Security and COPPA 

Your data are hold securely and all necessary measures are taken to keep them private. However you should know that there is always risk of unauthorized parties viewing or accessing your data since their transmitted through the Internet. Pollfish takes any necessary actions to comply with COPPA and protect the rights and safety of Minors. By Minors we mean individuals under the age of majority in their residence. Therefore, we delete any information and data that has come to our attention that is related with Minors without any notice. If anything has came to your attention regarding this issue please contact us immediately. 

Changes in this Privacy Policy may occur at any time without any prior notice. These changes will always be listed in this section of the website publicly accessible. For any changes that your prior consent maybe is required you will be informed by email in a reasonable time before those changes apply. By continuing to use our services and by not cancelling your account you agree and consent to these changes. You can cancel your account at any time. 

You consent to the collection, store and use of your data by Pollfish in a way as described in this Privacy Policy. By using Pollfish service you agree with policies as described in this website. 

**Survey Respondents**

Notice: Answering Pollfish surveys is completely voluntarily and you choose if you would like to answer a specific question in a Pollfish survey. 

What information does Pollfish collect about you? 

Pollfish collects your survey responses, which are later, processed by the platform and the survey creator. Your survey responses maybe used later on for better targeting and improve future Pollfish surveys. Your responses are submitted anonymously. We collect information about the device and the app you used to access Pollfish surveys such as IP address, device information and app used. Your IP address maybe used to identify your geographic location. Each response is associated with this information. Data about your behavior in a Pollfish survey lifecycle are collected and maybe used for statistic reasons and improvement of future services. In case you win you will be prompted to enter and submit your email to get further instructions on how to receive your award. Your email is kept securely and is not disclosed to any third party for any reason. Contact details that you maybe provide in order to get an award are kept private and are not disclosed to any third party for any reason except in the case that this is necessary on order to receive your award. 

How does Pollfish treat your information? 

Your survey responses are kept securely and are disclosed only to the survey creator. If you have any questions regarding the content of a survey please contact us to forward your concerns to the survey creator, which is responsible for the content of the survey. Pollfish platform use information collected about you (including device data, usage information, survey responses etc.) in order to improve Pollfish services and future surveys. Pollfish platform maybe use part of your survey responses in presentations, blog entries or other services provided by the platform, Your personal information is not disclosed to any third party advertising or marketing agencies. 

When and with whom we will share your information 

Your survey responses are disclosed only to the survey creator, which is the owner of this information. Anonymous survey responses as a whole maybe used for statistic showcases, info graphics, presentations, blog entries and other services that the platform provide. 

What actions can you make on your information 

You can request to update your personal and contact information that you submitted in order to receive an award. You cannot alter or request to alter any of the survey responses submitted through a survey lifecycle 

Security and COPPA 

Your data are hold securely and all necessary measures are taken to keep them private. However you should know that there is always risk of unauthorized parties viewing or accessing your data since their transmitted through the Internet. Pollfish takes any necessary actions to comply with COPPA and protect the rights and safety of Minors. By Minors we mean individuals under the age of majority in their residence. Therefore, we delete any information and data that has come to our attention that is related with Minors without any notice. If has came to your attention anything regarding this issue please contact us immediately. 

Changes in this Privacy Policy may occur at any time without any prior notice. These changes will always be listed in this section of the website publicly accessible. By voluntarily submitting your answers to Pollfish surveys you consent to the collection, store and use of your data by Pollfish in a way as described in this Privacy Policy. By using Pollfish service you agree with policies as described in this website. 

**App Developers**

What information does Pollfish collect about you? 

Registration Information. In order to register your app with Pollfish you have to register and create an account by providing your email and password. App Information. In order to enable Pollfish in your app you have to provide information about your app such as title, link etc. Pollfish Usage Information. Pollfish collects information about users behavior during Pollfish surveys lifecycle through your app 

How does Pollfish treat your information? 

Your registration information are kept securely and not disclosed to any third party for any reason. Your registration information data maybe used during assistance or customer support for providing better services to you. Your registration information maybe used for contacting you occasionally (for platform announcements, account activation etc.) Your app information maybe used for retrieving more information for your app from the relevant stores. Public available information regarding your app maybe shown at the website, showcases, presentations or other services or activities provided or used by Pollfish. Your app information maybe used in conjunction with your registration information in order to inform you about the Pollfish revenue and statistics through your app Pollfish usage information gathered through your app are you used by the platform to monitor the behavior of the platform and improve future services 

When and with whom we will share your information 

We do not disclose any of your personal information to any third party marketing or advertising agency. 

What actions can you make on your information 

You can update your registration information at any time To cancel or delete your account you should contact Pollfish team with your request at info@pollfish.com. You can enable or disable Pollfish surveys in your apps. 

Security and COPPA 

Your data are hold securely and all necessary measures are taken to keep them private. However you should know that there is always risk of unauthorized parties viewing or accessing your data since their transmitted through the Internet. Pollfish takes any necessary actions to comply with COPPA and protect the rights and safety of Minors. By Minors we mean individuals under the age of majority in their residence. Therefore, we delete any information and data that has come to our attention that is related with Minors without any notice. If has came to your attention anything regarding this issue please contact us immediately. 

Changes in this Privacy Policy may occur at any time without any prior notice. These changes will always be listed in this section of the website publicly accessible. For any changes that your prior consent maybe is required you will be informed by email in a reasonable time before those changes apply. By continuing to use our services and by not cancelling your account you agree and consent to these changes. You can cancel your account at any time. 

You consent to the collection, store and use of your data by Pollfish in a way as described in this Privacy Policy. By using Pollfish service you agree with policies as described in this website.
